Privacy Policy

Effective Date : August 22 ,2022  
   
COGNOSPHERE PTE. LTD. ("COGNOSPHERE", "we", "our", or "us") greatly recognize and value the privacy of people ("you" or "User"), who visit our websites, use or access our games, whether played on mobile devices, PCs, our websites or other approved platforms ("COGNOSPHERE Game(s)"), and/or otherwise use or access any of our provided services, including but not limited to customer supporting, marketing and advertising, and community services (collectively the "COGNOSPHERE Services").  
This Privacy Policy describes why and how we collect and use your personal data and the choices you have about your personal data which you provide or we collect in connection with the COGNOSPHERE Services. By accessing our websites or otherwise using the COGNOSPHERE Services, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and accepted the following terms. In the case you do not agree to any of the terms, you may immediately stop using our services.  
In the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, we will make an announcement in advance, disclose the details of the event and information about the successor, and with the express consent of you or your guardian again, your personal data may transfer to the successor of COGNOSPHERE. COGNOSPHERE may periodically modify, adjust or revise the terms of this Privacy Policy. The updated terms will be announced to you and obtain your consent again. You agree to check the updated terms regularly. If major clause changes are involved, we will make an announcement in advance.  
   
1\. What Data We Collect and Process  
OS type, OS version, UUID, device ID, device name, monitor information (width and height of the main monitor, number of monitors), CPU model, graphics card model, device memory usage (available memory/total memory), language used, Launcher version, game version, MAC address；  
When you use or interact with SDK and other third-party services that may be available on our services for users, please note it should be subject to their respective privacy policies.  
Unless with your express agreement, we will not collect personally identifiable information (PII) or sensitive personal information (SPI), such as TRUE name, address, telephone number, fax number, and e-mail address.   
   
2\. Why Do We Collect Your Personal Data  
For the purpose of providing quality services to you, we collect and process the data to:  
1) help you to download games;  
2) detect the reason for the download failure;   
3) protect the integrity, safety, and security of our services or our users, comply with legal obligations, and enforce compliance with the Terms of Service or other restrictions placed on your use of the COGNOSPHERE Services.  
For the purposes set forth above, our affiliates may be commissioned to process your information, provided that such affiliates comply with terms and conditions hereunder. Affiliate in this Privacy Policy shall mean an entity that directly or indirectly controls, is controlled by or is under common control with COGNOSPHERE hereto.  
In all of the above cases and purposes, you acknowledge and confirm that we may analyze, profile, segment, merge and/or update all collected data (regardless of an aggregated or individualized manner for the purposes of improving service quality and providing a better experience to users).  
   
3\. Who May Access Your Personal Data  
In addition to COGNOSPHERE and/or its affiliates, other parties may also access your personal data in the following situations. You acknowledge that you have foreseen and agreed to the occurrence of such disclosure when you provide your personal data.  
1) Competent Authorities  
We may provide certain portion of your personal data to judicial or administrative authorities as so requested. Besides, we may disclose certain portion of your personal data within a strictly limited scope of recipients when we reasonably think it is necessary to protect us, our users, or a portion of the public.  
In addition to be required by applicable laws, we reserve the right to disclose your personal data in the cases if we, in our good faith, believe that disclosing such data is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against you, if (a) you are violating any agreements between us, such as the Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy or otherwise damage us; (b) you are infringing third parties’ rights and interests (including but not limited to intellectual property rights); and/or (c) we believe that it is necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activities.  
2) Third-Party Contractors  
COGNOSPHERE works with a number of (if any) third-party contractors on or through our services. We do not sell your personal data and only share non-personally identifiable, aggregated, and public data with third parties.  
Please be aware that we cannot control the activities of such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they adhere to the same privacy policy as we do. Since those contractors may access your data as data controller and operate under their own privacy policies, we strongly encourage you to check their privacy policies on their official websites and learn more about their data processing practices.

4\. Data Retention  
We will keep your data for as long as needed to provide you the COGNOSPHERE Services unless deletion is carried out in accordance with your request. The locations of servers for the services include:  
(1) the United States,   
(2) Hong Kong;   
(3) the European Union；  
(4) Singapore；  
(5) Japan.  
You acknowledge and agree that your data will be processed on our servers which may not be located in your country of residence and can be accessed by our support, engineering and/or our affiliates around the world. No matter where our servers are located, we will make great efforts to take the appropriate safeguards to guarantee your rights in conformity with this Privacy Policy and any applicable laws.  
In the case you request to remove or delete your personal data, we will retain your data as long as necessary for our legitimate business interests, such as to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and/or enforce the agreements between us. Please note that the removal or deletion of any of your data may result in the termination of some of our applicable services.  
We will only store your information as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes for which the information is collected and processed or where the applicable law provides for longer storage and retention period. After that, your personal data will be deleted, blocked, or anonymized, as provided by applicable law.

5\. Your Rights  
If you request in writing, we will provide you a copy of your personal data in an electronic format after passing our verification process. You also have the right to correct or modify your data, have your data deleted, object how we use or share your data, restrict how we use or share your data, and make any other request as provided herein or regulated in the applicable regulations from authorities (including but not limited to the GDPR and the CCPA) through sending an email to the email address of our DPO (Data Protection Officer) as agreed in Article 10. Upon receiving your request via email, we will promptly conduct a verification process including but not limited to instructing you to provide information to confirm that you are the user from whom we have collected information, subject to the specific instructions of our DPO.  
(1) Right to Know About Personal Information Collected, Disclosed, or Sold  
You have the right to access your personal data that we hold about you, i.e. the right to require free of charge, (i) information whether your personal data is collected, used, disclosed, or sold, (ii) categories of your personal data which has been collected, (iii) categories of sources from which your personal data is collected, (iv) business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling your personal data (if any), (v) disclosure of sale of your personal data (if any): i.e. the categories of your personal data which has been disclosed or sold (if any) to third parties, the categories of third parties to whom your personal data was disclosed or sold (if any), statement regarding whether we have actual knowledge that we sell your personal data if you are under 16 years of age; and you have the right to require us to provide a duplicate of your personal data undergoing processing, subject to submitting a verifiable request in the form of email to our DPO’s email address as agreed in Article 10. You can also exercise the right to access your personal data through the privacy dashboard. According to our reasonable and unilateral judgement, if your verifiable request affects or will affect the rights or freedom of other users or is manifestly unfounded or excessive, we reserve the right to charge a reasonable fee (taking into account the administrative costs arising therefrom) or refuse to act on the request.

(2) Right to Rectify  
If we process your personal data, we shall endeavor to ensure by implementing suitable measures that your personal data is accurate and up to date for the purposes for which it was collected. If your personal data is inaccurate or incomplete, you have the right to obtain rectification of your inaccurate personal data without undue delay according to Article 16 of the GDPR and you can modify the information you provided via the privacy dashboard.

(3) Right to Request Deletion of Personal Information  
You have the right to obtain deletion of your personal data, if the reason as stated in Article 2 of this Privacy Policy does not exist anymore, or if there is another legal ground for its deletion, subject to submitting a verifiable request in the form of sending an email to our DPO’s email address as agreed in Article 10.  
You acknowledge and agree that as a result of deleting your HoYoverse Account, you will lose access to game related services, including the account information, subscriptions and game-related information linked to such HoYoverse Account and lose the possibility to access other services through the HoYoverse Account.

(4) Right to Object  
When our processing of your personal data is based on legitimate interests according to Article 6(1)(f) of the GDPR and/or Article 2 of this Privacy Policy or any other applicable laws in your country of residence, you have the right to object to our processing. If you object, we will no longer process your personal data unless there are compelling and prevailing legitimate grounds of processing as described in Article 21 of the GDPR or any other applicable laws in your country of residence; in particular, if the data is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims. You also have the right to lodge a complaint at a supervisory authority.

(5) Right to Restrict Processing  
You have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data under the conditions set out in Article 18 of the GDPR or any other applicable laws in your country of residence.

(6) Right to Personal Data Portability  
You have the right to receive your personal data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those data to another controller under the conditions set out in Article 20 of the GDPR or any other applicable laws in your country of residence.

(7) Right to Opt-Out of the Sale of Personal Information (if any)  
You have the right to opt-out of the sale of your personal data (if any) and require us to make a statement regarding whether or not we sell your personal data and provide an opt-out mechanism or link to it except as otherwise stipulated in the CCPA.

(8) Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of a Consumer’s Privacy Rights  
You have the right not to receive discriminatory treatment by us for the privacy rights conferred by the CCPA, namely that we shall not offer a financial incentive or a price or service difference due to your exercise of any of your rights under the CCPA unless such difference is reasonably related to the value of your personal data. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we have the right to deny your request to know, request to delete, or request to opt-out for reasons permitted by the CCPA or those regulations thereof, and such denial shall not be considered discriminatory.

(9) Right to Authorize an Agent to Make a Request on Your Behalf  
You have the right to authorize an agent on your behalf to make a request to know, delete, or opt-out under the CCPA. When you use an authorized agent to submit any request provided above, we may require you to provide signed permission to authorize your agent to do so for the purpose of verifying your own identity, and the official permission by your agent to submit this request. In the case of failure to provide any of the requested materials, to protect the user’s information and data security, we are entitled to denying such request.  
Notwithstanding the foregoing, if the applicable laws in your country of residence provide otherwise, the corresponding laws shall govern.

6\. Securing Your Data  
Pertaining to your use of our services, we have endeavored to take reasonable measures to prevent unauthorized access to or improper use of your personal data, such as organizational controls, technical protection, and other protection measures.  
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. While we strive to protect your personal data, we also remind you to be aware of the risks of hacking, cyberattacks, etc. on the Internet.  
Therefore, we urge you to take every possible precaution to protect your personal data when using our services, including but not limited to changing your passwords from time to time, not reflecting your real name or other personal data in registration, using a combination of letters and numbers when creating passwords, using a secure browser and/or taking other possible security measures. Please note for security reasons, we store passwords in encrypted form.  
Please be aware that advertisers or websites with links to and/or from our websites may collect personal data about you and this Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, those other advertisers or websites. We highly recommend that you read the privacy policy of such third-party websites which you may be directed to before providing any personal data.  
   
7\. Age Limits  
You represent that you are an adult or older in your country of residence (or at other age in your jurisdiction where you are classified as a majority) when using the COGNOSPHERE Services. If you are a minor child or under the legal age of majority ("Minor" or "Child"), please do not send any data about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address.  
We strongly urge parents to instruct their Child never to disclose personal data without the prior permission of parents. If we learn that we have collected personal data about a Child, we will delete that data as quickly as possible. Also, if you believe that we might have any data from or about a Child, please contact us.  
   
8\. Contact and Complaints  
As required by European data protection law, the Data Controller is COGNOSPHERE PTE. LTD. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or have any requests for resolving issues with your personal data, please contact us in the first instance by sending a letter to COGNOSPHERE PTE. LTD. at 6 RAFFLES QUAY #14-02 SINGAPORE (048580) or send an email to our data security officer at privacy@hoyoverse.com.

COGNOSPHERE PTE. LTD.   
Effective Date: August 22 ,2022
